Adarsh Verma

With one year of experience as a MERN Stack programmer specializing in Javascript and React.js, I have a proven track record of delivering exceptional customer experiences. I excel at creating a collaborative work environment, problem-solving, and ensuring customer satisfaction.

Address: 706 Ramdaspeth Near Police Station, Nagpur - 440010

Phone: 7719971779

Email: adarshverma549@gmail.com

GitHub: @AdarshTheki

LinkedIn: @adarshvermadeveloper

EXPERIENCE

Fsc Mihan, Nagpur - (Data Entry)

01/12/2022 to 25/10/2024 (22 month)

Our product is designed to meet the demands of your customer base on the Ajio E-Commerce App.

EDR Continuous Pvt.Ltd, Sitabuldi, Nagpur- (Data Entry)

01/02/2021 to 20/12/2021 (10 month)

Information technology & services Industry with (BPO Sector).

EDUCATION

Yashwantrao Chavan College, Nagpur MH. - (B.Com)

YEARS 2020 - 2023

Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com) degree, graduating with 78% from Yashwantrao Chavan College.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Next.Js App: <u>Admin Dashboard</u> + <u>E-Shopify Store</u>

Summary: Built a Next.js App with features like Product management (create, update, delete), Create all Data Tables for collections, products, orders and customers with Search bar, Handle Search, Add to Wishlist, Add to Cart functions, Checkout and create orders with Stripe and Recharts for graph.

Technologies: Next.js, Stripe, TypeScript, MongoDB, Clerk, React-Hook-Form, Tailwind & Shadcn UI, Cloudinary etc.

Overcame Challenges: Integrated Clerk with Next.js for seamless authentication, Optimized payment processing with Stripe, Ensured efficient database management with MongoDB.

OTHER PROJECTS LINK:

E-commerce | Video Streaming | Web-Music-Player

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Mongoose
- Node.js
- Express
- Next.js

SUPPORTING SKILLS

- Typescript
- Git & GitHub
- Tailwind & Shaden UI
- Appwrite & Firebase
- Cloudinary
- Figma Design
- Excel Sheet